



Ayberk Yavaş

Date of birth: 25/04/2003 | Nationality: Turkish | Email address: hireme@ayberkyavas.com | Website:

https://ayberkyavas.com/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayberksch/ | Github:

https://github.com/Ayberkyvs

ABOUT ME

a young Frontend Developer (for now), who is constantly improving himself, moving forward in my software adventure with my motto "I love the feeling of creation". I am most specialized in React, Router V6, Material Design, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS Modules, Databases, Accessibility & Usability, UX/UI Process, Figma, Version Control, Build Automation, Working w/API's

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2024 - 07/2024 Istanbul, Tuzla, Türkiye

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER (SPA) FREELANCE REFORM MARINE

Reform Marine offers customized solutions to the maritime industry as a company specialized in electrical systems maintenance and repair. I made single page web application for this brand. I used React, Tailwind, Ant Design, Context API, Hooks, PWA

Links https://github.com/Ayberkyvs/reformmarine | https://www.reformmarine.com/

07/2023 – 09/2023 Istanbul, Türkiye

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN DIGIME

I Have been working on a web application and solidified my JavaScript skills.

Link https://digime3d.com/

04/2023 - 06/2023 Istanbul, Türkiye

WEB DEVELOPER (SPA) FREELANCE PINYIN MARINE

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

11/2024

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT AND API'S freeCodeCamp

Website https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/ayberksch/back-end-development-and-apis

23/11/2024

TYPESCRIPT W/BOB ZIROLL Scrimba

Website https://scrimba.com/certificate-cert24zAw]77fGQG6kVUkgT9AGiob85Zjtc3fQEci

11/2024

META CERTIFIED FRONT-END DEVELOPER PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE Meta

At the end of a 7-month process, I completed a total of 400 hours and received 9 certificates and earned the Meta Certified Front-End Developer Professional Certificate.

Verify Links:

Coursera Profile: https://lnkd.in/dEAx3QDs

Badge: https://lnkd.in/dSty7jGE

Front-End Developer Professional: https://lnkd.in/dbXnkc9g

Coding Interview: https://lnkd.in/dekjSAhD

Front-End Developer Capstone: https://lnkd.in/d6vMiGa4
Front-End Developer Capstone Github: https://lnkd.in/dgdA6z4F

Principles of UI/UX: https://lnkd.in/dArzeFBd Advanced React: https://lnkd.in/dhXBJBhR React Basics: https://lnkd.in/dUUx2Ma9 HTML & CSS In Depth: https://lnkd.in/dDv2jm8w

Version Control: https://lnkd.in/dFp-izW5

Programming With JavaScript: https://lnkd.in/dib3|gea

Intro to Front-End: https://lnkd.in/dajrdC-a

Website https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/G1Z8VD7P21EA

02/2024

REACT ROUTER Scrimba

08/02/2024

ADVANCED REACT Scrimba

Website https://scrimba.com/certificate/uvvkNNUx/greact

01/2022 - 07/2024 Izmir, Türkive

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE: COMPUTER PROGRAMMING Izmir University of Economics

Website https://www.ieu.edu.tr/tr | Final grade 3.44/4

DIGITAL SKILLS

React Frame Work | Web development (HTML/CSS, JavaScript) | JavaScript | Git | react-router-V6 | HTML | Bootstrap | RESTful api | Github | HTML5 | Front-end Development with Vue.js and React.js | TypeScript | Photoshop And Figma | XML, JSON, YAML and others data models | SPA and PWA | Version Control System (Git) | npm / yarn | Basic Knowledge of SEO | Responsive, Cross Browser Development | CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind, SCSS, BEM...) | Vitejs | Figma | UX | UI | Web UI/UX Design | Rapid Prototyping | UX Research | Framer Motion | Hosting & DNS | SEO | Node.js / Express | Mongodb / Mongoose

PROJECTS

2024

Modern Portfolio

A portfolio website is a digital platform that showcases the professional endeavors, projects, and career progression of an individual or a company.

Links https://github.com/Ayberkyavas.v2 https://github.com/Ayberkyavas.com

12/2023 - 05/04/2024

Teknofest Rocket Competition

Contributed to fostering interest in space technologies and raising societal awareness in aviation, space, and technology. As a member of the software team, focused on:

- Designing a unique UI using React.
- Developing software for real-time processing of altitude, pressure, and GPS data with the ground station.

Link https://www.horizonrocket.com

04/2023 - 06/2023

Parkpin Smart Parking

Parkpin Smart Parking is an application that allows users to view all parking lots on a map, obtain information about the parking lots, reserve a spot, and make online payments.

Link https://github.com/LoyalEnv0y/ParkPin-V2

09/2022 - 01/2023

Gameathon Full Stack

Gameathon Events are organized by Izmir University of Economics Vocational School and participants are expected to develop a game from scratch within 24 hours. I not only provided the website with admin panel and application infrastructure for this event, but also served as the director throughout the event.

Links https://gameathon.ieu.edu.tr/ https://github.com/Ayberkyvs/gameathon/tree/main

NETWORKS AND MEMBERSHIPS

12/2023 - 05/2024 Izmir

Horizon Rocket Team

22/10/2022 - 05/2024 Izmir University of Economics

Gameathon Game Development

Gameathon Events are organized by Izmir University of Economics Vocational School and participants are expected to develop a game from scratch within 24 hours. I not only provided the website and application infrastructure for this event, but also served as the director throughout the event.

05/2024 Izmir University of Economics

6.Unigraph Design and Creativity Festival

Link https://www.ieu.edu.tr/tr/events/type/read/id/1618

2022 - 2024 Izmir University of Economics

Cyber Security Club

04/2024 Izmir University of Economics

Huawei Student Developers R&D Meeting

I attended the Huawei R&D Meeting organized by Huawei Student Developers. I had the opportunity to ask questions about Huawei's projects and entrepreneurship. Thank you to Huawei, HUAWEI Student Developers (HSD) Türkiye for organizing the event, and special thanks to Huawei R&D Director Fatih Mert and his team for their participation

RECOMMENDATIONS

Doğan İşleyen GM of EFOR Fuarcılık (Former GM of İZFAŞ)

He is a very ambitious and determined person, there is nothing he cannot do in the job he loves.

Phone (+90) 5336874545

Burak Erarslan Co-Founder of Pinyin Marine

He has developed himself in web services and has a strong communication skills

Email <u>burak.erarslan@pinyin-marine.com</u> | **Phone** (+90) 5373442566

Ertuğrul Aksel Founder at Serapore Machines

Thanks to Ayberk's innovative policies, development-oriented efforts, and time-saving solutions, our company has gained a significant market position since its inception. I extend my gratitude to them

Email ertugrul@serapore.com.tr | Phone (+90) 5324214816

Murat Albuz Plant Manager at Newarc

Kudos to Ayberk for driving our frontend development with creativity and efficiency. Their solutions have made a real impact!

Email murat@newarc.com.tr | Phone (+90) 5056814460

HONOURS AND AWARDS

31/05/2024

Certificate of Honor - İzmir University of Economics

I am an "Honour" Student with a GPA of 3.44 and I was entitled to receive this certificate.

The source of this resume is https://www.ayberkyavas.com. Sensitive information has been removed. Delete if you are not the recipient.

Last Updated, 23/11/2024